

Marwan Summakieh

Software engineer

Profile

I am a Passionate man who is interested in technology and video games. I have an artistic eye and strong work ethic, but also like to foster an element of fun. I also developed experience in motivation, critical thinking, and communication.

SKILLS

Java: 4/5

C#: 3/5

SQL: 3/5

Assembly: 2/5

React/React-Native:4/5

Certificates

<u>Introduction to Azure cloud services</u>

Programming in C#

Contact

Phone: 26822698

Email: marwansummakieh97@gmail.com

LinkedIn: Marwan Summakieh

LANGUAGES

English: Fluent in speaking and writing. Arabic: My native tongue. Danish: Beginner speaking and writing

EXPERIENCE

Behandlingsskolerne, Copenhagen — Automation engineer

March 2021 - June 2021

Built an on/off boarding system using office 365 and power automate

Konella group, Copenhagen — front end developer

January 2019 - February 2019

Was responsible for creating the website for the company and help out with repairs that come into the shop.

EDUCATION

Via University Collage, Software engineering

February 2019 - June 2022

Object Oriented programing with test driven development

PROJECTS

Point Of Sale: a mimic of the McDonalds ordering system, client server system using RMI. Github: https://github.com/MarwanSummakieh/Self-Ordering-Point-of-Sales-System

stem Message system: a very simple 3 Tier architecture first attempt built in C# and Java with MSSQL Database. Github:

https://github.com/MarwanSummakieh/Small-Messaging-App

Monitoring system: was part of a 12 people team working on the android application to monitor the environment in a train station using sensors.

Github: https://github.com/MarwanSummakieh/Train-Station-Monitor-App

 ${\bf Movie\ Info\ website}\hbox{:}\ {\bf Built\ with\ react\ and\ hosted\ on\ Azure.\ Github:}$

https://github.com/MarwanSummakieh/notpiratebay

VR Basketball: a small VR basketball game developed on Oculus quest with Unity. Github: https://github.com/xaviernadal/basketballVR

Bachelor's thesis: worked with two other students to develop an app that provides help in case of emergency Github:

https://github.com/MarwanSummakieh/bpr-app